nobroker.in 2017-02-26

# Broker free Apartments, shared accommodation, pg, houses for rent. NoBroker helps in renting apartment without broker

Loading...

####  Create a NoBroker account

###  Create a NoBroker account

#### Quick and Easy Social Sign Up 

or 

or 

No Password Required! We'll Never Post On Your Wall

###### By clicking 'Sign Up' you are accepting NoBroker's Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.

####  Use your NoBroker account

###  Use your NoBroker account

or 

#### Try a Quick Social Login

or 

_* NoBroker Makes No Posts on Your Wall_

##### One step sign-up to get owner details

Or use your email

is linked with the number . 

Do you want to update your number to ?

Phone number successfully updated

#### Please verify your mobile number below with the OTP sent.

Phone number successfully updated

Negotiate rent

Schedule a visit

Custom Message

Basic Free

New Property Alerts

Weekly

Date of Purchase

11/3/2015

Freedom 999

New Property Alerts

Daily

Online Rental Agreement

25% OFF

Personalised Recommendations

Date of Purchase

11/3/2015

Relax 1999

Personal Manager

New Property Alerts

Instant

Online Rental Agreement

25% OFF

Personalised Recommendations

Date of Purchase

11/3/2015

Assure 5999

Personal Manager

New Property Alerts

Instant

Online Rental Agreement Excluding Govt. Charges

FREE

Personalised Recommendations

Date of Purchase

11/3/2015

#### Congrats!

You have successfully subscribed to our rental Plan. Enjoy the Benefits. 

For assistance call us at : +91 92417-00000 . *All Plans are Valid for 3 months period, terms and conditions apply

Click below to post your property for rent

Give a missed call on the below number to list your property for sale

### Select a day and time below and meet the owner without any hassle

Please specify you are an owner or a tenant! 

We'll get in touch with you to post your TO-LET details.

We'll get in touch with you to gather your requirements.

## Privacy Policy

###### Last Updated on 20 February, 2014

##### NoBroker.in is operated by NoBroker Technologies Solutions Pvt Ltd.,

#### Creation of Account

    1. To access and use some section on NoBroker.in that are restricted only to registered users, you need to create an account on NoBroker.in 
    2. To create an account we need your verified email address or Mobile number, which could then be used to login to NoBroker.in 
    3. You have to accept the terms of service before creating an account on NoBroker.in 
    4. NoBroker.in reserves the right to the creation of the account on its website and can reject the creation based on content, information, broker listing or any other reason it may find appropriate without stating and is not liable to give a clarification or reason for rejecting the account creation 
    5. NoBroker.in reserves the right to charge or change the charges for creation of the account or for allowing access to contact details of landlord /tenant anytime that it deems necessary 

#### Invitations to join NoBroker.in

    1. Email addresses to which invitation(s) are sent, are stored in the system for logging purposes. 
    2. We may use these email addresses to send periodic notifications about the service. Receivers can opt out and will never be sent any email from NoBroker.in 

#### Personal information

    1. We ask for some personal information when you create a NoBroker.inaccount, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. 
    2. To provide you with access to the appropriate Network, we will require you to provide the name and contact information described above, and may also request that you update or verify this information from time to time. By using the Site, you agree to provide accurate information, and to cooperate with any NoBroker.in personnel to ensure accuracy. 
    3. As a NoBroker.in user, you can create a profile that includes personal information regarding your property or requirement plus other content, such as photos. This information may be accessed and viewed by other users of NoBroker.in 
    4. When you send messages through NoBroker.in, we collect and maintain information associated with those messages, including email addresses and content. 
    5. When you send and receive SMS messages to or from the NoBroker.in website, we collect and maintain information associated with those messages, such as the phone number, the wireless carrier associated with the phone number, the content of the message, and the date and time of the transaction, for logging purposes. 
    6. We take the privacy of our users very seriously. 
    7. NoBroker.in will have a right to use the information to provide personalized advertisements and offers, or to include that information in compilations developed by NoBroker.in 

#### General Provisions

    * By agreeing to post a property listing or requirement at NoBroker.in or responding to and advertising on NoBroker.in or by using the services of NoBroker.in, the user hereby acknowledges and allows NoBroker.in, its partners and other users of the site to get in touch with him/her from time to time for intimating the users on events, potential buyers, tenants or properties they might be interested in. This could include offers to upgrade to premium services, information, as well as promotions.NoBroker.in can use the user's email address and/or contact numbers for this purpose irrespective of the user's registration with the "National Do Not Call Registry" and will override any such registrations. 

#### E-mails and Opt-out

You may opt-out of receiving notifications from us by sending us an email at hello@nobroker.in. Unregistered users who receive e-mails from us may also opt-out of receiving further e-mails by following the instructions contained in our e-mails. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you notice of any updates to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy. 

#### Security

    * Your account is password protected. We use industry standard measures to protect the personal information that is stored in our database. We limit the access to your personal information to those employees and contractors who need access to perform their job function, such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security on NoBroker.in, please contact us. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that your personal information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. 

##### You hereby acknowledge that NoBroker.in is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

#### Contacting us

    * You can email us on hello@nobroker.in 

Click below to post your property for rent

Give a missed call on the below number to list your property for sale
